Stanley Woodward
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Material, 1916-1970, Series 9:; (Boxes 6-7; 0.75 linear feet)
  - Reproductions of Art Work, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 55-56)
  - Booklet The Keystone Barrage, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 1)
  - Brochures for Art Schools, 1936-1937, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 2)
  - Brochures for Books, 1947, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1932-1957, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1920-1969, Series 10:; (Boxes 7-8, OV 9; 11 folders)
  Photographs are of Woodward, members of his family, friends, studio, and art works. The photographs of the U. S. Army Air Forces include an image of Woodward with Jack Dempsey. Albums 1 and 2 include photographs of art classes and of Woodward painting outdoors at various locations including Laguna Beach and Palm Springs, California, St. Augustine, Florida, and Rockport, Massachusetts. Album 3 also contains photographs of Woodward at his easel, but includes photographs of notable friends including Janis Carter, Jeanne Craine, Bette Davis, Rita Hayworth, and Gary Merrill.
  - Photographs of Woodward, 1965, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Family Members and Friends, 1939-1942, undated, (see also OV 9) (Box 7 (pam), Folder 7)
  - Photographs of the U. S. Army Air Forces at McChord Field, Washington, 1943 (Box 7 (pam), Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Woodward's Studio, 1969, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 9)
  - Photograph Album 1, 1920-1940, (see also Box 8) (Box 7 (pam), Folder 10)
  - Negatives of Art Work, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 11)
  - Photographs of War Monuments, 1969, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 7 (pam), Folder 13)
  - Photograph Album 2, 1948-1953 (Box 8 (sol))
  - Photograph Album 3, 1954-1966 (Box 8 (sol))
  - Two Oversized Panorama Photographs of Woodward's Classmates in the U. S. Army Air Force Officer Training Schools in Miami, Florida, and in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1942 (Box OV 9)